http://www.tamko.com/Legal#privacy

Home Gallery
Where Do I Begin?
Below-Grade
Windows,
Click to add
(?)
Password
Click to add
(?)
Remember me on this device
Login
Log in
Search
Popular searches:
TRANSACTING BUSINESS WITH TAMKO BUILDING PRODUCTS LLC
Only the corporate officers of TAMKO Building Products LLC (hereinafter TAMKO®) have the legal authority to bind the corporation to any obligation and/or agreement whatsoever; provided however, in certain cases specific authority has been delegated in writing to certain managers.
No contract or agreement, or modification or amendment to any contract or agreement, to which TAMKO® is a party will be valid or binding upon TAMKO unless agreed to in a formal written document signed by a corporate officer of TAMKO or by a manager to whom authority has been delegated in writing.
The only authorized corporate officers of TAMKO are the President, Executive Vice-President, a Vice-President, the Treasurer, and the Corporate Secretary.
No other employee of TAMKO has authority to bind the corporation in any manner whatsoever.
Communication with TAMKO
Copyright
Courtesy
California Transparency in Supply Chains Act
Find a TAMKO Pro
Privacy Policy
California Privacy Policy
Third-Party Content
User End Rights
Warranties
Communication with TAMKO
Correspondence with TAMKO, including but not limited to e-mail, becomes the property of TAMKO upon delivery.
TAMKO respects website user’s right of privacy and will handle personally identifiable information in accordance with the Privacy Policy provided below.
Back to Top
Copyright
This Web site is Digital Media Copyright(c) 1997-2020, TAMKO Building Products LLC.
All rights reserved. Copyright in this document and all accompanying material collectively known as the “TAMKO website” are owned by TAMKO.
Copyright is in effect even for pages and material without the copyright notice, as these are implied to belong to the TAMKO Web site.
Back to Top
Courtesy
TAMKO appreciates the efforts of others to spread the word about our high quality products, including companies and organizations providing a link to TAMKO’s website.
To foster consistent messaging, please inform us in advance of your intention to publish any link to the TAMKO website.
Back to Top
California Transparency in Supply Chains Act of 2010
TAMKO’s manufacturing facilities are exclusively located in the United States.
These facilities are operated in accordance with all federal, state, and local workplace safety and labor laws.
Moreover, TAMKO maintains and enforces a Code of Ethics and Business Conduct which requires compliance with all applicable laws.
Currently, TAMKO does not actively verify product supply chains to evaluate and address risks of human trafficking and slavery; audit suppliers for compliance with company standards for trafficking and slavery; require direct suppliers to certify that materials incorporated into our products comply with the laws regarding slavery and human trafficking of the countries in which they are doing business; maintain internal accountability standards and procedures for employees or contractors failing to meet company standards regarding slavery and trafficking; or provide company employees and management training on human trafficking and slavery.
TAMKO has internally assessed the risk of human trafficking in its supply chain and determined the nature of its business model, locations of direct suppliers, and nature of materials they supply make it unlikely that human trafficking or slavery is involved.
Back to Top
Find a TAMKO® Pro
Selection of a roofing contractor or installer is an important decision made solely by the homeowner.
TAMKO does not recommend or endorse any particular contractor or TAMKO Pro. You should evaluate
several contractors and select the one you believe best fits your specific needs. You should choose a
contractor who is properly licensed, financially sound, properly bonded and insured and who has a
good reputation in your community.
TAMKO does not guarantee the workmanship of any contractor or TAMKO Pro. TAMKO's Limited Warranty and
the Mastercraft Limited Warranty Enhancement exclude coverage for shingles that are not installed
strictly according to TAMKO's installation instructions. Any dispute between you and your contractor does
not involve TAMKO. YOU AGREE TO RELEASE TAMKO BUILDING PRODUCTS LLC, ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AGENTS,
EMPLOYEES, AFFILIATES AND REPRESENTATIVES FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, DAMAGES, DEMANDS, LOSSES, CAUSES OF ACTION
AND ACTIONS (INCLUDING CONSEQUENTIAL AND INCIDENTAL DAMAGES), WHETHER KNOWN OR UNKNOWN, AND WHETHER
ACCRUED OR ACCRUING, WHICH YOU MAY HEREAFTER HAVE ON ACCOUNT OF OR RELATED TO YOUR SELECTION OF A CONTRACTOR
AND/OR ANY DISPUTE YOU MAY HAVE WITH YOUR CONTRACTOR.
TAMKO Pros must periodically meet certain qualifications to become or remain a TAMKO Pro; however,
TAMKO does not make any representations or warranties regarding the reputation, skill level,
qualifications or expertise of TAMKO Pros. TAMKO Pros are not employees of, agents of, or affiliated with, TAMKO in
any manner.
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT TAMKO DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, INCLUDING ANY
WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE OR PURPOSE OR ANY OTHER WARRANTY OF ANY KIND
WHATSOEVER, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO TAMKO's SELECTION PROCESS FOR THE TAMKO
PRO PROGRAM.
TAMKO Building Products LLC (“TAMKO”) designates certain roofing products installers as a TAMKO® Pro
Certified Contractor (“TAMKO Pro”) under its TAMKO Pro program upon receipt of the installer’s $250
application fee and, upon approval and receipt of the installer’s $1000 TAMKO Pro sign-up fee, TAMKO
provides the installer with the following: a non-exclusive license to offer (at no additional cost
to homeowners) TAMKO’s Mastercraft Limited Warranty Enhancement on Heritage® Vintage®, Heritage®
Premium, and Heritage Woodgate® products; access to Greensky to assist homeowners with financing for
installation of a new roof; sales leads through HomeAdvisor’s Profinder as well as through TAMKO’s Pro Certified
Contractor Locator website link; discounts for use of EagleView estimating technology, mHelpDesk
software, JobNimbus software, Digital Fusion website services, Ford X-plan pricing, and Staples
office products; TAMKO’s Pro Certified Contractor App; and TAMKO customer apparel, business cards, and
other custom marketing tools. A TAMKO Pro (and other roofing product installers) may receive rebates or
other consideration from TAMKO in connection with the purchase and use of TAMKO products.
Back to Top
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: February 3, 2017
TAMKO respects your privacy.
To this end, TAMKO follows the Privacy Policy outlined below to help protect personally identifiable information obtained during your use of this website.
By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described in this notice.
Information Collected
During your use of this website or a TAMKO mobile application, we obtain certain information about you in order to service your business and enhance our services. The personally identifiable information collected depends on the website features you select, but it can include your name, company name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. Certain features require users to create a username and password that are also collected. Additionally, TAMKO’s website uses “cookies” to collect information, including your IP address and webpages visited on the site, to help us manage our site and improve your experience. TAMKO’s site currently does not recognize “do not track” signals from a website browser.
Use & Sharing
We limit the collection of personal information to that which is necessary for the purposes of efficiently conducting our business. The primary use of the information is to determine the method and most appropriate information to send you in response to your requests. TAMKO is the sole owner of the information collected at our site. When a user requests a quote from TAMKO Pro(s) through our website, we provide the user’s contact information to the selected TAMKO Pro(s). We do not sell, share, or rent information to other third parties or partners. Personal information about our visitors or former customers is not disclosed to any other third parties, except as required by law (such as a subpoena), as may be appropriate to protect against fraud or illegal activity, or for the safety of customers, employees, or property.
Important Information
Children’s Privacy: TAMKO does not direct services to or knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.
Privacy Policy Changes: TAMKO may change, modify, or add terms to this Privacy Policy as needed. Material changes to this policy will be reflected on this notice. We recommend you periodically visit this page to review updates.
Information Review: If you believe the information requires correction or amendment, please send the corrected or amended information in an e-mail to the following address: info@tamko.com.
If you have specific questions that are not answered by this notice, please send your inquiry to the following e-mail address: info@tamko.com.
Back to Top
California Privacy Policy
Last Updated: December 20, 2019
Download a copy of TAMKO's California Privacy Notice (PDF)
This California Privacy Policy supplements the information contained in TAMKO’s Privacy Policy and applies solely to consumers who reside in the State of California. TAMKO adopts this notice to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) and other California privacy laws.
Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this Notice.
Information We Collect
In the course of its business, TAMKO collects certain “Personal Information,” as that phrase is defined by the CCPA. Within the last twelve (12) months, TAMKO collected the following categories of Personal Information from consumers who reside in the State of California1:
Category
Examples of Information that May Be Collected by TAMKO
A. Identifiers
A real name, alias, postal address, unique Personal Information identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or Social Security number.
B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))
A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information.
C. Commercial information
Records of Personal Information property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
D. Professional or employment-related information.
Current or past employment or professional experience or performance.
E. Internet or other similar network activity
Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.
F. Geolocation data
Physical location or movements.
1Some types of Personal Information fit into multiple categories and are, therefore, listed multiple times. TAMKO will not collect additional categories of Personal Information without providing you notice.
TAMKO obtains the categories of Personal Information listed above from the following sources:
Categories A, B, C, and D:
Directly from the consumer. For example, from submissions through our website portal or forms, or website usage details collected automatically.
From third-parties that interact with us in connection with the services we perform.
Categories E and F:
From activity on our website (www.tamko.com). For example, from submissions through our website portal or website usage details collected automatically.
Use of Personal Information
TAMKO may use the Personal Information described in Categories A, B, C, and D for one or more of the following business or commercial purposes:
To fulfill or satisfy the reason the consumer provided the information. For example, if a consumer shares his/her name and contact information to ask a question about our products or services, TAMKO will use that Personal Information to respond to the inquiry. Similarly, if the consumer provides Personal Information to make a warranty claim, TAMKO will use that information to administer the claim.
To provide the consumer with requested information, products, or services.
To provide, support, and/or develop TAMKO’s Website, products, or services.
To create, maintain, and/or secure a consumer’s account with TAMKO.
To process a consumer’s requests, transactions, and/or payments and prevent transactional fraud.
To carry out TAMKO’s obligations and/or enforce its rights arising from any contracts entered into between a consumer and TAMKO, including for billing and collections.
For testing, research, analysis, and/or product development.
To respond to law enforcement requests or as otherwise required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
As described to the consumer when collecting the Personal Information.
Auditing related to a current interaction with the consumer and concurrent transactions.
Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.
Performing services on behalf of the business, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services.
Undertaking activities to verify, improve, upgrade, enhance, or maintain the quality or safety of TAMKO’s products or services.
Attracting consumers to buy, rent, lease, join, subscribe to, provide, or exchange products, goods, property, information, or services, or enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial transaction.
TAMKO may use the Personal Information described in Categories E and F for one or more of the following business or commercial purposes:
To provide, support, and/or develop TAMKO’s Website, products, or services.
To create, maintain, and/or secure a consumer’s account with TAMKO.
To process a consumer’s requests, transactions, and/or payments and prevent transactional fraud.
For testing, research, analysis, and/or product development.
To respond to law enforcement requests or as otherwise required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
As described to the consumer when collecting the Personal Information.
Auditing related to a current interaction with the consumer and concurrent transactions.
Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.
Performing services on behalf of the business, including providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services.
Undertaking activities to verify, improve, upgrade, enhance, or maintain the quality or safety of TAMKO’s products or services.
Attracting consumers to buy, rent, lease, join, subscribe to, provide, or exchange products, goods, property, information, or services, or enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial transaction.
TAMKO will not collect additional categories of Personal Information or use the Personal Information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.
Disclosing Personal Information
TAMKO does not, and will not, sell Personal Information (including the Personal Information of minors under the age of 16). TAMKO may disclose (and, over the preceding 12-months, has disclosed) the Personal Information described in Categories A, B, C, and D for a business or commercial purpose to the following categories of third parties:
Government agencies and courts, required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
Vendors providing services to TAMKO.
Right to Know About Personal Information Collected or Disclosed
Consumers who reside in the state of California have the right to request that TAMKO disclose certain information to them regarding TAMKO’s collection and use of their Personal Information (hereafter called a “Request to Know”). Requests to Know may also be submitted by the consumer’s “authorized agent,” as that term is defined by the CCPA. Specifically, a consumer or his/her authorized agent may submit a Request to Know:
The categories of Personal Information TAMKO has collected about that consumer within the preceding 12 months.
The categories of sources from which that Personal Information was collected about.
TAMKO’s business or commercial purpose for collecting that Personal Information.
The categories of third parties with whom TAMKO has shared that Personal Information.
The specific pieces of Personal Information TAMKO has collected about that consumer within the preceding 12 months.
This information will only be provided after the requestor’s identity has been verified. However, even where the requestor’s identify has been verified, TAMKO will not disclose a consumer’s Social Security number, driver’s license number or other government-issued identification number, financial account number, any health insurance or medical identification number, an account password, or security questions and answers.
TAMKO is not obligated to provide this information to the same consumer more than twice in any 12-month period.
Right to Request Deletion of Personal Information
Consumers who reside in the state of California have the right to request that TAMKO delete Personal Information collected or maintained by TAMKO (hereafter called a “Request to Delete”). Requests to Delete may also be submitted by the consumer’s “authorized agent,” as that term is defined by the CCPA.
Submitting a Request to Know or Request to Delete
A consumer who resides in California, or his/her authorized agent, may make a Request to Know or Request to Delete the consumer’s personal information by:
Calling 1-800-641-4691;
Submitting an online request at https://www.tamko.com/about/contact-us; or
Emailing info@tamko.com
Within 10 days of receiving a Request to Know or Request to Delete, TAMKO will confirm receipt of the request. TAMKO will endeavor to respond to a consumer request within 45 days of its receipt. If TAMKO requires more time to respond, TAMKO will inform the consumer of the reason and extension period (not to exceed an additional 45 days) in writing.
A consumer submitting a Request to Delete must separately confirm the request. After receiving a Request to Delete, TAMKO will send a separate communication with instructions on how to confirm the Request to Delete.
Before processing a Request to Know or Request to Delete from an authorized agent, TAMKO will require:
A notarized copy of the consumer’s written permission authorizing the agent to make the request; and
That the consumer verify his/her identity directly with us, as explained above.
Consumers may submit the information listed above to info@tamko.com. Authorized agents may also submit the notarized copy of written permission to info@tamko.com. If an authorized agent has a valid power of attorney under California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465, proof of the power of attorney may be submitted instead.
Verifying a Request to Know or Request to Delete
Verification of the requestor’s identity will be accomplished as follows:
Where the requestor seeks only information regarding the categories of Personal Information TAMKO has collected regarding a specific consumer, TAMKO will verify the requestor’s identity by matching at least two data points provided by the requestor with data points previously provided by the consumer. Depending on the information previously provided by the consumer or collected by TAMKO, these data points may include address, telephone number, business affiliation, and/or email addresses.
Where the requestor seeks specific pieces of Personal Information TAMKO has collected regarding a specific consumer, TAMKO will verify the requestor’s identity by matching at least three data points provided by the requestor with data points previously provided by the consumer, as well as requiring a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that the requestor is the consumer whose personal information is the subject of the request. Depending on the information previously provided by the consumer or collected by TAMKO, these data points may include address, telephone number, business affiliation, and/or email addresses.
Where the requestor seeks deletion of Personal Information TAMKO has collected regarding a specific consumer, TAMKO will verify the requestor’s identity by matching at least two data points provided by the requestor with data points previously provided by the consumer. Depending on the information previously provided by the consumer or collected by TAMKO, these data points may include address, telephone number, business affiliation, and/or email addresses.
If necessary to verify a consumer’s identity, TAMKO may ask for additional information that will help do so. TAMKO will only use that additional information for any purpose other than verification process.
Non-Discrimination
The CCPA provides consumers residing in the State of California with the right not to receive discriminatory treatment for exercising their privacy rights under the CCPA. TAMKO will not discriminate against a consumer for exercising rights under the CCPA by:
Denying goods or services.
Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
Providing a different level or quality of goods or services.
Suggesting that the consumer may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about TAMKO’s privacy policies and practices, you may contact us at by email at info@tamko.com or by submitting an online request here.
Back to Top
Third-Party Content
Last Updated: October 4, 2017
TAMKO’s website may, from time to time, include discussion forums, or other interactive areas, including the ability to post comments and upload content (“Interactive Area”).
Any use you make of any Interactive Area, including the uploading, distribution, posting or publishing of any message, data, information, images, text or other material (“Content”) is conditioned on your agreement not to do any of the following:
Upload to, distribute, post or otherwise publish through TAMKO’s website any Content that is unlawful, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, indecent, lewd, harassing, threatening, harmful, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, abusive, inflammatory or otherwise objectionable;
Upload, transmit or post any Content that would constitute or encourage a criminal offense, violate the rights of any party, or that would otherwise create liability or violate any local, state, national, or international law;
Upload, transmit or post any Content that may infringe any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other intellectual or proprietary right of any party. By posting any Content, you represent and warrant that you have the lawful right to distribute and reproduce such Content;
Impersonate any person or entity or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity; and
Without TAMKO’s written permission, distribute or publish unsolicited promotions, advertising or solicitations for funds, goods or services, including junk mail and spam.
TAMKO takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any Content posted or uploaded by you or any third party, or for any mistakes, defamation, slander, libel, omissions, falsehoods, obscenity, pornography or profanity you may encounter. As a provider of interactive services, if any, TAMKO is only a forum and is not liable for any statements, representations, or Content provided by its users.
By submitting Content to TAMKO, you hereby grant TAMKO a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, sublicenseable and transferable license to use, reproduce, distribute, repost, transmit, prepare derivative works of, display, and perform the Content in connection with TAMKO ‘s (and its successors' and affiliates') business, including without limitation for promoting and redistributing part or all of the Content (and derivative works thereof) in any media formats and through any media channels. Without limiting the foregoing, TAMKO reserves the right to use any Content as it deems appropriate, including, without limitation, deleting, editing, modifying, rejecting, or refusing to post it. TAMKO is under no obligation to edit, delete or otherwise modify Content once it has been submitted to TAMKO. TAMKO shall have no duty to attribute authorship of Content to you, and shall not be obligated to enforce any form of attribution by third parties.
By virtue of using the Interactive Area, you hereby declare that (a) you do not require that any personally identifying information be used in connection with the Content, or any derivative works of or upgrades or updates thereto; (b) you have no objection to the publication, use, modification, deletion and exploitation of the Content by TAMKO or its licensees, successors and assigns; (c) you forever waive and agree not to claim or assert any entitlement to any and all rights, including without limitation moral rights of an author and intellectual property rights in any of the Content; and (d) you forever release TAMKO, and its parents, affiliates, subsidiaries, licensees, successors and assigns, from any claims that you could otherwise assert against TAMKO by virtue of any such rights.
Back to Top
User End Rights
Any person or entity (user) is hereby authorized to view, print, and distribute these documents (files) subject to the following conditions:
Files may be used for informational purposes only. User cannot make money from or commercialize files without prior written permission.
Any copy of files or portions thereof must include the TAMKO legal notice (this entire page) as well as any specific legal notices appended to that collection of pages.
Uses, in whole or in part, include but are not limited to: viewing, transmitting, printing, copying, distributing, and manipulating. All forms of uses are subject to further restrictions set by TAMKO.
Absolutely no reappropriation of files (e.g., packaging into CD-ROMs) without prior written permission from TAMKO.
Back to Top
WARRANTY DISCLAIMER/LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
You agree that your use of TAMKO’s website shall be at your sole risk. To the fullest extent permitted by law, TAMKO and its officers, directors, shareholders, affiliates, employees, agents, and representatives of any type disclaim all warranties in connection with the website and your use thereof. The website information is provided "as is" without warranty of any kind, either expressed, implied, or statutory, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement.
TAMKO makes no warranties or representations about the accuracy or completeness of the information contained on the site or any linked site and assumes no liability or responsibility for any (1) errors, mistakes, or inaccuracies in the content; (2) personal injury or property damage, of any nature, resulting from your access to or use of TAMKO’s website or any linked website; (3) any unauthorized access to or use of TAMKO’s secure servers and/or any and all personal or financial information stored therein; (4) any computer viruses, bugs, or the like which may be transmitted to or through our website by any third-party; and/or (5) any errors or omissions in any content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any content posted, e-mailed, transmitted or otherwise made available via the website or a related communication. TAMKO does not ENDORSE, warranty, guarantee, or assume responsibility for any product or service offered by a third-party linked to the website. References to corporations, their services and products, are provided “as is” without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied. In no event shall TAMKO be liable for any direct, indirect, special, exemplary, punitive, incidental, or consequential damages of any kind, or any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data or profits, whether or not advised of the possibility of damage, and on any theory of liability, including TAMKO’s own negligence, however caused, arising out of or in connection with the use of this information.
Regarding warrantability of products and brands mentioned on this Website, they are provided for informational purposes only. No warranties are legal, binding or otherwise effective until transfer of sale and backed by signed written documents.
This website may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Changes are periodically added to the information herein; these changes will be incorporated in new editions of the website. TAMKO reserves the right to make improvements and/or changes in the product(s) and/or the program(s) described in this website at any time without notice.
Back to Top
Residential Roofing
Shingle Colors
Shingle Styles
Roofing Accessories
Home Gallery
Roof Visualizer
Visualizer Help
